Guide to the Daily Worker and the Daily World Negatives Collection PHOTOS.223.001
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VI: Contact Sheets, 1918-2006
  - Subseries A: Contact Sheets with Shoot Numbers
    - Peace Meeting Sponsored by SANE and United Auto Workers, Local 1199 Hall (44th Street and 8th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include John Lindsay, William F. Ryan, Kurt Vonnegut, Jr., Leonard Woodcock, Edward Condon, David Livingston, Sanford Gottlieb and Bella Abzug. Photos by Bill Andrews., Feb 26, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710034)
    - Demonstration Against War Taxes, New York Telephone Company (14th Street near 3rd Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 2, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710039)
    - Judy Collins Departing with Peace Delegation to Paris from John F. Kennedy Airport, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 3, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710041)
    - Peace Symbol on Hand. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 3, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710042)
    - National Peace Action Coalition Press Conference, Overseas Press Club (40th Street), New York, New York. Participants include Leon Davis and Corliss Lamont (frames 21-23), Ossie Davis and Ruth Gage Colby. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 4, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710044)
    - Women Strike for Peace Demonstration Against United States Invasion of Laos, Public Library (42nd Street and 5th Avenue) to William F. Buckley's office at New York Post (45th Street and Lexington Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Bella Abzug and Cora Weiss. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 5, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710046)
    - Rally in Support of Jailed Teachers Union Leaders, Robert Treat Hotel, Newark, New Jersey. Participants include Robert Seldon, Albert Shanker and Charles Marcionti. Photos by Robert McMillan, Mar 7, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710047)
    - Demonstration by Bronx Mothers Against Space Program and for Funding Poverty Programs, City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 8, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710049)
    - International Women's Day Rally in Honor of Angela Davis, Audubon Ballroom, 166th Street and Broadway, New York, New York. Participants include Eduardo Gallegos Mancera (Venezuelan Parliament member), Roque Ristorucci, Charlene Mitchell and Doris Turner. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 8, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710050)
    - Doll and Signed Poster Sent to Angela Davis from Children in the Soviet Union, Committee to Defend Angela Davis office, 150 5th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 8, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710051)
    - David Perez with Sports Trophy, Jesus Colon's Apartment (St. Marks Street and Brooklyn Avenue), Brooklyn, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710053)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Leaders, 23rd West 26th Street, New York, New York. Gus Hall, Hy Lumer, George Meyers, Daniel Ruben and Henry Winston pictured. Photos by Ted Reich., Mar 12, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710054)
    - Rally to Defend Ericka Huggins and Bobby Seale, New Haven, Connecticut., Mar 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710057)
    - Demonstration Against War Taxes, Internal Revenue Service, 120 Church Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 15, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710059)
    - Demonstration for Angela Davis, Foley Square Federal Court House, New York, New York. Participants include Mary Lou Sanchez, David Poindexter, Gil Green, John Abt, Jarvis Tyner and Louise Patterson. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 16, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710060)
    - Louise Patterson at Daily World., Mar 19, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710061)
    - Teachers On Strike, Washington Park, Newark, New Jersey. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 26, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710062)
    - Unemployed Demonstration to Support Blumenthal-Santucci Bill, 12 West 14th Street Welfare Center, New York, New York. Demonstration organized by People's Cause., Mar 26, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710063)
    - Jewish Defense League Pickets Communist Party of the United States of America Headquarters, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 30, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710065)
    - Communist Party of the United States Headquarters Bombed by Jewish Defense League, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Bill Stanby (frames 22-24), Dave Buxombaum (frames 39-41), Hy Lumer (frame 13), Matty Berkleheimer (frame 11) and Mark Beiller (frame 5) pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 30, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710066)
    - Spring Offensive Against War, Racism, Poverty and Repression, Central Park Mall, New York, New York. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, HOsea Williams, Frederick Douglas Kirkpatrick, Benjamin Spock, Chris Ijima, Joanne Miyamoto, The Harriet Tubman Freedom Singers, Al Evanoff and Manuel Vasquez. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 3, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710070)
    - Spring Offensive Against War, Racism, Poverty and Repression, March from Union Square to New York Stock Exchange, New York, New York. Participants include George Wiley, Doris May Ponselle, Hosea Williams, Dave Dellinger, Al Hubbard, Sidney Peck, Bella Abzug and Ralph Abernathy. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 5, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710072)
    - Demonstration Against A&P Minority Hiring Practices, March from Washington Square Methodist Church (4th Street near 6th Avenue) to 420 Lexington Avenue, New York, New York. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, Judy Edelman and Vicky Stevens. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 6, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710073)
    - Demonstration Against A&P Minority Hiring Practices, March from A&P Office (44th Street and Lexington Avenue) to A&P Store (31st Street and 3rd Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Hosea Williams and Bob Johnson. Photos by Bob Calvert., Apr 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710076)
    - Jim Dillon, Mike Jay Kaufman and Rick Nagin at Daily World., Apr 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710077)
    - Inquiring Photographer, Union Square, New York, New York., Apr 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710078)
    - Ragtime Piano Concert, WBAI-FM Studio, 359 East 62nd Street, New York, New York. Participants include Bill Bolcom (frames 3-4, 19-20), Dave Jasen (frames 5-7, 10, 13, 16), Dan Paget (frames 8-9, 17-18) and Ken Cooper (frames 11-12). Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 11, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710079)
    - Demonstration for Day Care at Public Library, 161st Street and Columbus Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 14, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710080)
    - Social Service Union Employees Union Demonstration for New Contract, City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 14, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710081)
    - Claude Lightfoot at Daily World., Apr 16, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710083)
    - Sallye Davis (mother of Angela Davis), Southern Conference Educational Fund meeting, Hottel Roosevelt (45th Street and Madison Avenue), New York, New York. Dorothy Burnham Lumer, Virginia Collins and John Hulett also pictured. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 18, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710085)
    - Jane Hodes., Apr 18, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710086)
    - Peace March, Washington, D. C., 14th Street and Pennsylvania Avenue, Capitol Steps. Participants include John Kerry, Sallye Davis, Louise Patterson, Ralph Abernathy, David Livingston, Frederick Douglas Kirkpatrick, Pete Seeger, Barbara Dane, Coretta Scott King and Bella Abzug. Photos by Bill Andrews., Apr 24, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710090)
    - New York City Municipal Workers Demonstrate Against Budget Cuts, City Hall, New York, New York., Apr 27, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710091)
    - May Day, Santiago, Chile. Salvador Allende (frames 12-15, 19-23), Rick Nagin (frames 2-3, 19-21, 37) pictured. Photos by Teresa Silva., May 1, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710093)
    - African American and Puerto Ricans Demonstrate Againt Vietnam War and New York State Budget Cuts, Nelson Rockefeller's Office (22 West 55th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 5, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710094)
    - Peace Rally, Bryant Park (40th Street and 6th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include David Livingston and John Kerry. Photos by Bill Andrews., May 5, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710095)
    - Henry Winston 60th Birthday Celebration, Hilton Hotel, New York, New York. Participants include Barbara Dane, Jacob Malik, Fern Winston, Esther Cooper Jackson, James E. Jackson, Gus Hall, Helen Winter, Victoria Stevens, Daniel Rubin and Jarvis Tyner. Photos by Bill Andrews., Mar 14, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710097)
    - Henry Winston 60th Birthday Celebration. Participants include John Abt, Rasheed Storey, Jarvis Tyner, Charlene Mitchell and Arnold Johnson. Photos by Garry Tyler., May 14, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710098)
    - Demonstration Against Greek Fascist Junta, Greek Day Parade, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., May 16, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710099)
    - Black Panther and Harlem Five Press Conference, Abraham Lincoln Project Community Center (133rd Street and 5th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Clark Squire, Cattarra, Curtis Powell, Sayeed Saladeen and Hannibal Ahmad., May 17, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710100)
    - Young Workers Liberation League Pickets Subversive Activities Control Board, 26 Federal Plaza, New York, New York. Participants include Jarvis Tyner (frames 21), Jim Davis (frame 15), David Poindexter (frame 24), Jose Stevens (frame 9) and Mike Zagarell (frame 32). Photos by Bill Andrews., May 18, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710102)
    - Pete Seeger with Frederick Douglas Kirkpatrick, Children's Art Exhibit from Cuba. Photos by Garry Tyler, May 1971 - Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710115)
    - El Mundo Nuevo Day Care Center (community-controlled day care center), 583 Vermont Street, Brooklyn, New York., Jun 2, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710121)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Wildcat Strike Against New York Joint Board of Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 32 West 15th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 2, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710122)
    - Inquiring Photographer., Jun 3, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710123)
    - Israel Bonds Employees On Strike, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 4, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710124)
    - Rent Strike, 157-161 West 105th Street, New York, New York. George Hickerson (Vice President, Morningside Renewal Council) seated at desk. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 5, 1971 - Jun 10, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710126)
    - Inquiring Photographer. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 5, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710127)
    - New York City Municipal Workers On Strike to Protest Loss of Pension, New York City Parks Department (64th Street and 5th Avenue), New York, New York., Jun 7, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710128)
    - Victor Brady, Steel Drum Player from Virgin Islands, Central Park (60th Street and 5th Avenue), New York, New York., Jun 7, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710130)
    - Philadelphia Textile Cutters on Strike, New York, New York. Participants include Rick Nagin, George Morris, Jose Ristorucci and Carmen Ristorucci. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710131)
    - Rent Strike Conference, Columbia University, New York, New York. Organized by Metropolitan Council on Housing. Participants include Jane Benedict (frame 22). Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 12, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710134)
    - Puerto Rican Day Parade. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710135)
    - Puerto Rican Day Parade. Photos by Sheldon Ramsdell., Jun 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710136)
    - Window Washer at Work. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 16, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710137)
    - International Ladies Garment Workers Union Pension Rally, 37th Street and 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Sheldon Ramsdell., Jun 17, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710138)
    - Demonstration Against Extension of Draft Law, Times Square, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jun 23, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710139)
    - Alexander Dobkin Art Show, Local 1199 Hall (43rd Street and 8th Avenue), New York, New York. Alexander Dobkin, Jack Levine, Leon Davis, Doris Turner and Moe Foner pictured., Jun 23, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710140)
    - Printing and Processing Daily World at Prompt Press, 423 West 25th Street, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710144)
    - United Parcel Workers Union on Strike. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710145)
    - Demonstration Against School Budget Cuts, City Hall, New York, New York. Participants include Albert Shanker and Victor Gotbaum. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710146)
    - Day Care Center. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710148)
    - Aretha Franklin, Apollo Theater, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710151)
    - Pete Seeger and Frederick Douglass Kirkpatrick Perform for Children. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710152)
    - Martin Luther King, Jr.'s Hopemobile, a Project of Many Races Cultural Foundation. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710154)
    - Inquiring Photographer, Harlem, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710155)
    - Inquiring Photographer, on Black Panthers. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jun 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710156)
    - Picnic at Dorothy Robinson's House, Jamaica, Queens, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 6, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710160)
    - Sit-in by Supporters of United Farm Workers to Protest Use of Non-Union Grapes, Heublein Liquors, 8 East 55th Street, New York, New York., Jul 7, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710161)
    - Anti-War Advertisements for "Help Unsell the War" Campaign, Gallery at 74th Street and Madison Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710162)
    - Women Protest Arrest Without Bail of Prostitutes, Criminal Court, 100 Centre Street, New York, New York., Jul 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710163)
    - Communications Workers of America Picket AT&T, 17th Street and 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 14, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710164)
    - Pickets at Western Union. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 20, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710166)
    - Signing Petitions in Support of Bail for Angela Davis, National Maritime Union, 12th Street and 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 22, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710167)
    - Puerto Rican Art Show. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 22, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710168)
    - Simon Gerson at Daily Worker., Jul 22, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710169)
    - Press Conference in Support of Jimmy McDonald (producer/host of "Black Perspective on the News"), Local 1199 (8th Avenue and 43rd Street), New York, New York. Joe Walker (editor of "Muhammad Speaks) pictured. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 23, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710171)
    - Daily World Picnic, Camp Midvale, New Jersey. Participants include Dave Gordon (frames 3, 34), David Poindexter (frames 4, 24-26), Ken Newcomb (frames 4-5, 28, 44), Lenore Beillor (frame 2), Ron Tyson (frame 8), Rick Nagin (frame 4) and Dorothy Robinson (frame 33-34). Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 24, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710172)
    - People's Park Built by Squatters, Plaza Caribe (112th Street and Broadway), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 25, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710173)
    - Gathering Signatures of Unemployed, Welfare Center (20th Street and 6th Avenue), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 28, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710174)
    - Ted Bassett and Garry Tyler at Daily World., Jul 28, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710175)
    - Communications Workers of America Reject Contract [signed by] Thomas Beirne, Manhattan Center (34th Street and 8th Avenue), New York, New York. Participants include Daniel Keenan (President, Local 1103) and Ricky Carnivale (President, Local 1101)., Jul 29, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710176)
    - Demonstration Against Massacre of Sudan Communist Party Leaders and Members by Gaafar Nimery, Sudan Mission to United Nations, 48th Street and 3rd Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Jul 29, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710177)
    - Daily World Staffers at Work, 205 West 19th Street, New York, New York. Ron Tyson, Stephanie Tyson, Tom Foley, Constant Ponsolle, Bill Andrews, Jerry Cook, Betty Gumovich, Ruth Beinart, Ben Levine, Richard Greenleaf, Carl Winter, Simon Gerson, Seymour Joseph, Erik Bert, Ted Bassett, Vicky Morris, Sue Elan, Conrad Komorowski, Mike Jay, Rick Nagin, Phil Bonosky, Jose Pedro Perez and Donna Ristorucci pictured. Photos by Ellen Perlo., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710178)
    - Communications Workers of America On Strike Against AT&T, Detroit, Michigan. Photos by Mary Louis., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710181)
    - Sit-in at Day Care Center, Washington Heights (neighborhood), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710182)
    - Harlem Urban Development Corporation (HUDC). Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710183)
    - New York City Municipal Workers Laid Off. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710184)
    - Art Blakey and Betty Carter, Urban League, Chicago, Illinois. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710185)
    - African American Children, Chicago, Illinois. Photos by Garry Tyler., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710186)
    - Pat Bonner-Lyons (member of Young Workers Liberation League), Candidate for School Committee, Boston, Massachusetts. Photos by Bob Guild., Jul 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710188)
    - Hiroshima Day Anti-War Protest, 47th Street and Broadway. Participants include Pete Seeger and Frederick Douglad Kirkpatrick. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 6, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710191)
    - African American Children at Play, Newark, New Jersey. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 7, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710192)
    - Demonstration Against Nuclear Bombing of Nagasaki, New York Stock Exchange (Broad and Wall Streets), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710193)
    - Demonstration Against British Imperialism in Northern Ireland, British Consulate, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 10, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710194)
    - Communications Workers of America Picket AT&T (Broadway and Dey Street). Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 10, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710195)
    - Southern Christian Leadership Conference Convention, New Orleans, Louisiana. Participants include Ralph Abernathy, Coretta Scott King, Eugene McCarthy, Rosa Parks, Al Hubbard, Dave Dellinger, James Groppi and Daniel Ellsberg. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710197)
    - Demonstration Against Richard M. Nixon, Knights of Columbus, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 18, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710198)
    - Communist Party of the United States of America Candidates, 23 West 26th Street, New York, New York. Gus Hall (President) and Jarvis Tyner (Vice President) Pictured. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 19, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710199)
    - Service Employees International Union, Local 1199 Salute to Angela Davis, Local 1199, 43rd Street near 8th Avenue. Photos by Garry Tyler., Aug 20, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710202)
    - Graphic Art from Ben Goldstein's Collection. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 23, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710203)
    - March and Rally for Women's Equality, from 43rd Street and 5th Avenue to Central Park Mall, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Aug 26, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710209)
    - Scenes in Puerto Rico. Photos by Vicky Morris., Aug 1971 - Sept 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710211)
    - Clean Up for Future Home of Harlem Institute for Marxist Studies, 2715 8th Avenue, New York, New York. Jose Stevens and Ron Tyson pictured. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710212)
    - Demonstration in Support of Bangladesh. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 9, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710213)
    - Social Welfare Center, Hoboken, New Jersey. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 10, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710214)
    - African American Day Parade, Harlem, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 12, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710215)
    - Demonstration Against Attica Prison Massacre, Nelson Rockefeller's Office (55 West 55th Street), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Sep 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710216)
    - Attica Prison Massacre. Herman Badillo (frame 29), Arthur Eve (frames 26-28, 35) and Bobby Seale (frame 10) pictured., Sep 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710217)
    - Rally and March Against Attica Prison Massacre, Union Square, New York, New York. Participants include Dave Dellinger, Norma Becker and John Frones., Sep 13, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710218)
    - March Against Attica Prison Massacre, Harlem, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 18, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710219)
    - Georgia Johnson (mother of George and Jonathan Jackson) at press conference, 52nd Street and 7th Avenue, New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Sep 21, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710221)
    - March to Albany, New York to Protest Attica Prison Massacre. Photos by Jose Perez., Sep 23, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710223)
    - Angela Davis Day, March and Rally from 59th Street and 5th Avenue to Central Park Bandshell, New York, New York. Participants include Ron Dellums (frames 6-14, 44-1), Ossie Davis (frames 15, 21-24), David Livingston (frames 16-17), Louise Patterson (frame 18), Jarvis Tyner (frames13-20), Arthur Eve (frames5-7), Dick Gregory (frames 15-20), Pete Seeger (frames 37-39), Haywood Burns (frames 40-41), Sallye Davis (frames 22-26) and Henry Winston (frames 34-36., Sep 25, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710224)
    - Black Expo, Chicago, Illinois. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 27, 1971 (Box 32, Shoot 710225)
    - Marcus Tyler Murphy, Chicago, Illinois. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710229)
    - Palisades Amusement Park, New Jersey, Shortly Before It Is Closed and Destroyed. Photos by Garry Tyler., Sep 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710231)
    - Service Employees International Union, Local 1199 workers protest wage freeze and Vietnam War, Foley Square, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 1, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710232)
    - New York Longshoremen On Strike, Pier 90 (50th Street and Hudson River) and Pier 92 (52nd Street and Hudson River), New York, New York. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 6, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710236)
    - Congress of Racial Equality (CORE) Convention. Participants include Shirley Chisholm, Roy Innis and James Farmer. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 7, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710238)
    - Leafletting for October 13th Moratorium Day, Garment District, New York, New York. Participants include Mike Zagarell and Marc Beallor. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 7, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710239)
    - Puerto Ricans Protest Lack of Public Housing, City Hall, New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 8, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710240)
    - Demonstration in Support of Funding for Housing Renovation, 21st Street and 8th Avenue, New York, New York. 11 people, mostly women, arrested. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 11, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710242)
    - Art by African American artists. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 12, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710244)
    - October Moratorium Day. Labor-Sponsored Peace Rally, 37th Street and 7th Avenue. Participants include John Lindsay, Emil Mazey, Cleveland Robinson, David Livingston and Ken Newcomb. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 13, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710245)
    - Signing Petitions to Free Angela Davis, New Your Committee to Free Angela Office, 150 5th Avenue, New York, New York. Participants include Louise Patterson and June Jasper. Photos by Bill Andrews., Oct 14, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710247)
    - Demonstration Against Humanitarian Award to Nelson Rockefeller, Hotel Hilton (6th Avenue and 53rd Street), New York, New York. Photos by Garry Tyler., Oct 14, 1971 (Box 33, Shoot 710248)